

Sigit Wahyudi

FRONT END DEVELOPER



sigitwahyu.my.id

Kadipaten, Jendi, Selogiri, Wonogiri, Indonesia +6281227951097 sigitwahyu.mutu@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hello, I'm Sigit Wahyudi, a student of the Informatics Study Program at the Muhammadiyah University of Surakarta. I like programming since 2nd grade of high school until now I have been studying web programming for more than 3 years and now I am focusing on developing web using JavaScript language.

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Engineer

2022 - Present (CV ZAMANNOW, Sukoharjo)

Apply web design principles and responsibly ensure that the company's website runs well across multiple devices.

Work with developers, designers, and other product owners.

Create reusable code.

Freelance Front End Developer

2020 - Present (Fastwork, Indonesia)

Responsible for any display that the user will see

Make code for easy maintenance

Ensuring the suitability of the design on the web

Participated in continuous improvement by generating

suggestions, engaging in problem-solving activities to support
teamwork

EDUCATION

informatics Engineering

2020 - Presents (Muhammadiyah University of Surakarta)

Computers and Networks

2017 - 2020 (Muhammadiyah Vocational High School 1 Sukoharjo)

Skills

Communication Skills, Likes learn new things, Critical Thinking, Problem Solving, Creativity, Team & Time Management, Leaderships, Likes challenges

Programming Skiils

HTML, CSS (TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, SASS), JavaScript (ReactJs, NextJs), Styled Component

Languages

Indonesia (Excellent) English (Good)

Achievement

2nd place in the UI/UX competition at the 2022 BEM FKI Communication and Informatics Festival.

Organization

Head of social affairs - Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika UMS 2021-2022.

Staff og Social Affairs - Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika UMS 2020 - 2021

Certificate

Belajar Fundamental Front-End Web
Development - Dicoding
Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Web dengan
React - Dicoding
Responsive Web Design - Freecodecamp

Latest Project

Shopcut - shopcut.netlify.app
I made this to learn nextjs, rest API and react context and as a final project.

Abinawa - abinawa.netlify.app
This is a 3D wayang information web
that I made with my group for the
Student Creativity Program (PKM).

Crown Clothing - cloth-crwn.netlify.app Learning outcomes react, redux, styled component, firebase, and react router dom.

Digipack - digipack-final.netlify.app one of the projects when I was a freelance UI engineer